What is your process?
あなたの処理は何ですか?
It is a sexual education process.
性育処理です
As a stomach, we as a stomach, and as a penis, it feels good.
お腹として、僕らがお腹として、おちんちん気持ちよくすんだよ
One step at a time to make yourself feel better.
気持ちよくしていこうと、1つずつ
Konochin
このちん
Please do as much as possible.
ち んにいっぱいなしてください
Oh, let's go.
ああ、いくよ
Oh, open your mouth.
ああ、口開ける
Ah, let's go.
ああ、いく
Please give us more players.
もっといっぱい選手ください
Hello, open your mouth.
もしもし、口開けて
Open your mouth.
口開けろ
Stick out your tongue.
舌出せ
substitute
代わり
To.
に
I'm grateful.
感謝 しているんだよ
Get the players out.
選手出しよ
Dad is about to lose.
お父さんが負けしかけしか
ah.
ああ
I'll put it out.
出すよ
While carefully tweezing
丁寧にピンスしながら
hey.
ね
It's also in your mouth.
口 にもついてるからさ
Because there aren't many more.
もっといないからさ
This too.
これも
I look forward to your continued support.
これからもよろしくね
So double pince,
そこでダブルピンスして、
I will reward you with a penis.
お ちんちんご報酬させていただきます
I will continue to reward you with a lot of penises.
これからもいっぱいおちんちんご報酬させていただきます